Oh, me!
Yeah, me, too!
(Mrs Cooper:)Coming up.
(Leonard:)I don't really
feel I deserve it.
(Howard:)That was a big
sticky mess,
(Howard:)but... I think I got it.
(Raj:)Looks good.
Yeah.
(Penny:)Look at that.
(Bernadette:)You cleaned it up
all by yourself.
(Howard:)Yes, I cleaned it up
all by myself.
(Howard:)Honestly, I don't know
why you complain so...
(Howard:)Okay, maybe I missed one spot.
(Howard:)Just leave.
(Mrs Cooper:)I'm so glad
that you and I were able
(Mrs Cooper:)to bury the hatchet.
Me, too.
(Dr Hofstadter:)And I respect your right
to your beliefs.
(Mrs Cooper:)And I will
pray for you.
(Leonard:)Okay, Mom, let's get you
back to your hotel
(Leonard:)before anyone says
anything else.
BEVERLY:
One moment.
(Dr Hofstadter:)There's something
I need to say to you.
(Leonard:)Oh, really? That's too bad.